Guide to the ILGWU. Local 89. Luigi Antonini correspondence, 1919-1968
ILGWU. Local 89. Luigi Antonini correspondence,
- Series III. Speeches, 1935-1948.
  - Speeches: June 1949-Sept. 1950., 1949-1950 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Oct. 1950-51., 1950-1951 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Jan. 1952-Feb. 1953., 1952-1953 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Mar. 1953 - July 1954., 1953-1954 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Aug. 1954-Dec. 1955., 1954-1955 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Jan. 1956-Dec. 1957., 1956-1957 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Jan, 1958-Feb. 1959., 1958-1959 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Mar. 1959-June 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: July 1960-Sept. 1961., 1960-1961 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Oct. 1961-Dec. 1962., 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Jan. 1963-Apr. 1964., 1963-1964 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: May 1964-Aug. 1965., 1964-1965 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: 1965-0ct. 1966., 1965-1966 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Nov. 1966-July 1968., 1966-1968 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Speeches on tapes: (incomplete): (1), (1), 1954 (1) 1955 (2), 1957 (11), (24), (23), 1954-1957 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Speeches on tapes: 1960(46), 1961 (40)., 1960-1961 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Speeches on tapes: 1961 (cont'd.), 1962 (40), 1963 (19)., 1961-1963 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Speeches on tapes: 1964 (36), 1965 (39)., 1964-1965 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Speeches on tapes: 1966 (19), 1967 (18),(20)., 1966-1967 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Cases, Executive and Main District Board., 1934-1970 (Box 80, Folder 1)